You're saying I should hitch a ride on a boat
with you hairballs and watch the Fire Festival?
毛玉たちの船に便乗して送り火を見ろというのか
Me?
わしに
You sure can be cheeky sometimes.
図々しいことを言う
Mom's going to treat us to
.bowls of sushi and stuff.
母がちらし寿司をご馳走するとか
Sushi made by a tanuki?
The hair will get stuck in my throat!
狸の作った寿司なんぞ毛が喉に詰まる
ふう
Anyway, if you feel like it, please come to
.Tadasu-no-Mori tomorrow evening at seven.
ともかく気が向いたら明日の夜七時に
糺の森へお越しください
I might stop by if I remember. Who knows.
覚えておったら行くかもしれん 行かぬかもしれん
Wait, but don't count on me showing up.
あてにせずに待っておけ
He'll be there.
来るな
Imitating the various beauties of
.nature is nice and sophisticated,
花鳥風月を真似るのも風流だが
but imitating humans is
.probably the most fun of all.
やはり一番味があるのは人間を真似ることであろう
For some reason, it's always entertaining to
.mingle in at their events and enjoy ourselves.
そうやって人間の行事にどこまでも
相乗りして遊ぶのが
何だか妙に面白い
"It's just another reflection of our idiot blood."
それは阿呆の血のしからしむるところだ
Dad used to say that with a smile
whenever my brothers or I caused mischief
我々兄弟が何か悪さをして騒ぎを起こすたびに
or got into a mess of some kind.
父はそう言って笑った
The night of the Gozan Fire Festival
.is the highlight of summer.
夏の風物詩たる五山の送り火の宵
We tanuki would get caught up in the humans'
.merriment and throw our own parties,
浮かれる人間どもに調子を合わせて
我ら狸が浮かれるのも
though this, too, is probably another
.reflection of our idiot blood.
結局はその阿呆の血のしからしむるところであろう
面白くない世の中
omoshiroku nai yo no naka
You just have to make
Original     Work
Morimi Tomihiko
"Uchouten Kazoku"
Original     Work
Morimi Tomihiko
"Uchouten Kazoku"
Original     Work
Morimi Tomihiko
"Uchouten Kazoku"
Original     Work
Morimi Tomihiko
"Uchouten Kazoku"
Gentousha Publishing
Original     Work
Morimi Tomihiko
"Uchouten Kazoku"
Gentousha Publishing
Original     Work
Morimi Tomihiko
"Uchouten Kazoku"
Gentousha Publishing
Original     Work
Morimi Tomihiko
"Uchouten Kazoku"
Gentousha Publishing
Original     Work
Morimi Tomihiko
"Uchouten Kazoku"
Gentousha Publishing
Original     Work
Morimi Tomihiko
"Uchouten Kazoku"
Gentousha Publishing
Original     Work
Morimi Tomihiko
"Uchouten Kazoku"
Gentousha Publishing
Original     Work
Morimi Tomihiko
"Uchouten Kazoku"
Gentousha Publishing
Original     Work
Morimi Tomihiko
"Uchouten Kazoku"
Gentousha Publishing
Original     Work
Morimi Tomihiko
"Uchouten Kazoku"
Gentousha Publishing
Original     Work
Morimi Tomihiko
"Uchouten Kazoku"
Gentousha Publishing
Original     Work
Morimi Tomihiko
"Uchouten Kazoku"
Gentousha Publishing
Original     Work
Morimi Tomihiko
"Uchouten Kazoku"
Gentousha Publishing
Original     Work
Morimi Tomihiko
"Uchouten Kazoku"
Gentousha Publishing
Original     Work
Morimi Tomihiko
"Uchouten Kazoku"
Gentousha Publishing
Original     Work
Morimi Tomihiko
"Uchouten Kazoku"
Gentousha Publishing
Original     Work
Morimi Tomihiko
"Uchouten Kazoku"
Gentousha Publishing
Original     Work
Morimi Tomihiko
"Uchouten Kazoku"
Gentousha Publishing
Original     Work
Morimi Tomihiko
"Uchouten Kazoku"
Gentousha Publishing
Original     Work
Morimi Tomihiko
"Uchouten Kazoku"
Gentousha Publishing
Original     Work
Morimi Tomihiko
"Uchouten Kazoku"
Gentousha Publishing
Original     Work
Morimi Tomihiko
"Uchouten Kazoku"
Gentousha Publishing
Original     Work
Morimi Tomihiko
"Uchouten Kazoku"
Gentousha Publishing
Original     Work
Morimi Tomihiko
"Uchouten Kazoku"
Gentousha Publishing
Original     Work
Morimi Tomihiko
"Uchouten Kazoku"
Gentousha Publishing
Original     Work
Morimi Tomihiko
"Uchouten Kazoku"
Gentousha Publishing
Original     Work
Morimi Tomihiko
"Uchouten Kazoku"
Gentousha Publishing
Original     Work
Morimi Tomihiko
"Uchouten Kazoku"
Gentousha Publishing
Original     Work
Morimi Tomihiko
"Uchouten Kazoku"
Gentousha Publishing
Original     Work
Morimi Tomihiko
"Uchouten Kazoku"
Gentousha Publishing
Original     Work
Morimi Tomihiko
"Uchouten Kazoku"
Gentousha Publishing
Original     Work
Morimi Tomihiko
"Uchouten Kazoku"
Gentousha Publishing
omoshiroku sureba ii sa
this dull world more interesting
面白くすればいいさ
omoshiroku sureba ii sa
this dull world more interesting
“つまらねえ”のが口癖なのは
tsumaranee no ga kuchiguse nano wa
Some people love to claim that something is boring
それこそホントにつまらない
sore koso honto ni tsumaranai
That habit is the most boring thing of all
文句を言うのは簡単だけど
monku wo iu no wa kantan dakedo
It's easy to complain about stuff
dareka wa nannmo kurenai
but it doesn't do any good at all
誰かは何もくれない
dareka wa nannmo kurenai
but it doesn't do any good at all
hashiranai kedo tomari wa shinai
That sort of useless waste of time
走らないけど止まりはしない
dare ni mo nagareru ahou no chi
runs in our idiot blood
誰にも流れる阿呆の血
sawageba sawagu hodo kakitateru
Just party on and on, and the more you do
騒げば騒ぐ程かき立てる
nanto subarashiki hibi
the more awesome will be your days
なんと素晴らしき日々
omoshiroku nai yo no naka
You just have to make
面白くない世の中
omoshiroku sureba ii no sa
this dull world more interesting
面白くすればいいのさ
jibun de mitsukerya
The things you find for yourself in this world
自分で見つけりゃ
hodohodo ni paradaisu da
quickly turn it into a little paradise
ほどほどにパラダイスだ
ki ga tsukeba itsu datte
Before you know it,
気がつけば何時だって
ki ga tsukeba itsu datte
Before you know it,
uchouten jinsei da
you live a life of pure ecstasy
有頂天人生だ
uchouten jinsei da
you live a life of pure ecstasy
Episode Four
The Daimonji Leisure Cruiser Battle
Teakettle energy
For Master
Akadama
Teakettle energy
For Master
Akadama
Teakettle energy
For Master
Akadama
Teakettle energy
For Master
Akadama
Teakettle energy
For Master
Akadama
Teakettle energy
For Master
Akadama
Teakettle energy
For Master
Akadama
Teakettle energy
For Master
Akadama
Teakettle energy
For Master
Akadama
Teakettle energy
For Master
Akadama
Is Master really going to come?
先生は本当に来られるのか？
Why don't you guys transform into a couple
of the Seven Lucky Gods yourselves?
お前たちも七福神に化けたらどうなんだ
ふうう
んう
Sorry, big bro. I can't do it.
兄ちゃんごめん 無理
んん
Father would always transform
into Hotei. In his memory—
父上はいつも布袋様に化けておられた
その父上を偲ぶためにも
No tanuki likes transforming under someone
.else's orders. That's just how we are,
化けろと言われると…
化けたくなくなるのが狸の情というものだよ
big bro.
兄貴
うう
Yo!
よう
ん
Sorry to keep you waiting.
待たせたね
あ ああ
Father must be grieving in
.the afterlife by this point.
これでは父上も冥土で嘆かれているに違いない
As long as we're all smiling,
I'm sure Father's smiling too.
皆が笑ってれば 父上も笑ってるはずだよ
んん
You're just overthinking things.
兄貴は難しく考え過ぎだ
See? Here he is.
ほら来た
ああ
んん
うーん
ん？
ふう
いっ　ん
ん
んよいしょっと
Why isn't he coming over?
先生 どうして来ないの？
はあ まったく手間のかかる
What a piece of work.
Huh? Oh, Master!
おや
これはこれは先生
Well, if it isn't Yasaburou.
矢三郎ではないか
What a coincidence!
Are you taking a walk?
偶然ですね
お散歩ですか
Indeed. It's such a nice, cool evening.
うむ涼しくて気分のいい宵だな
That's wonderful.
それは結構なことで
By the way, Master, are you aware
that tonight is the Gozan Fire Festival?
時に先生
今宵は五山送り火であることにお気づきですか
Oh, is it?
おや そうか
We were just planning to fly out in the inner parlor
.we borrowed from you and watch the fires.
これから先生にお借りした奥座敷を使って
送り火を見物しようと企んでいたところです
If you're not too busy,
would you like to come with us?
もしお急ぎでなければご一緒にいかがですか
It's not much, but we've
.prepared food and drink.
ささやかながら酒と飯なども用意してございます
That's right. You did mention
something about that, didn't you?
そういえばそんなことを言っておったなあ
I was just thinking I'd like to take a break.
ちょうど一服したいと思っていたところだ
I suppose it wouldn't hurt
.to join you for a little while.
少しぐらいなら構うまい
い んん
Is that you, Yaichirou?
What's with that form?
お前 矢一郎か 何故そのような格好をしておる？
ん 今宵は無礼講です 薬師坊先生
I'm abandoning formality this
.evening, Master Yakushibou.
I like to have some fun now and then, too.
たまには私も遊ぶのですよ
は
By the way, when is Ben—
ところで
あ べん…
Welcome, Master!
先生 いらっしゃいませ
んん
だあ
はあ 茶釜に飲ませるのはもったいない
It's such a waste to give such
fine port to the teakettle!
For Master
Akadama
ああ
By the way, when is Ben—
ところで べん…
Master, over there is Mount Nyoigatake.
-先生
-ん？
あちらが如意ヶ嶽ですよ
Can you see Daimonji?
大文字が見えますか
はあ　見えておる
I can. I can indeed.
見えておるとも
ずず
ずず ああ
By the way, when is Benten coming?
ところで弁天はいつ来るのだ？
For Master
Akadama
Teakettle energy
I believe she knows about the
.party today, so she might come.
Teakettle energy
今日の宴はご存知のはずですから…
-来るかもしれませんね
-ああ
It sure is great that you're giving that
blasted teakettle so much to drink!
茶釜風情にそんなに飲まさずとも良かろう
But, Master,
そうは言っても先生
if we don't let the teakettle drink too,
it'll get upset and we'll fall.
茶釜にも飲ませないと
へそを曲げて落ちてしまいますよ
That might be a problem
for you fur-brains, but—
落ちて困るのは毛玉どもであろうが
Now, now, Master.
まあまあ先生
Don't be so stubborn.
そう固いこと言わず
あ んん
ん
Don't get too close to
.the edge, or you'll fall.
あんまりそっちへ行ってはダメよ 落ちるから
I know!
はーい
The Ebisugawas are here.
夷川が来たよ
え
んん
ああ
Look, there's Soun.
見ろ 早雲がいる
ふふふふーん
Boom!
どーん
Those jerks! Do they
wanna go again this year?
あんにゃろう 今年もやる気か
Let's just call the Manpukumaru incident
.an unfortunate accident.
万福丸は不幸な事故だったんだ
The fireworks they set off just
happened to start a fire. Okay?
たまたまあちらが打ち上げた花火が引火しただけだ
そういうことにしておけ
Like hell it's okay!
納得いかん
The Nise-emon election is coming up.
偽右衛門選挙が近いんだ
Please don't cause trouble.
面倒事は起こさんでくれ
Besides, relatives shouldn't
.squabble amongst themselves.
それに親戚同士でいがみ合ってはいかん
ん？
Just dropping by.
邪魔するよ
おうおう
Oh, it's you.
何だお前か
Well, hello to you too.
おやおやご挨拶だね
Were you expecting some
other tengu besides me?
わしじゃない他の天狗でも来るのかい？
Quiet, you.
うるさいわ
Welcome. It's good to see you.
ようこそいらっしゃいました
ああ
How dull. So this is what it's like
.to see it from down here.
つまらんな
下界から見ればあんなものか
You don't want to go back there?
あそこへ戻りたくはないかね？
At this point, I don't even care.
It would only spell more trouble.
構わぬ 今更 面倒が増えるばかりだ
The False Nyoigatake Incident
was really something, wasn't it?
偽如意ヶ嶽事件 ありゃあ痛快だったな
Shimogamo Souichirou.
Now he was a real tanuki.
下鴨総一郎
確かに一廉の狸であった
ん
It sure has been a while since then.
もう随分と経つがね
I guess it was right around the time
.Shimogamo Yasaburou was born.
ちょうど下鴨の矢三郎が生まれた頃だったか
Back then I was a little fuzzball
.the size of a dandelion head.
たんぽぽぐらいの毛玉でした
Souichirou was already
Nise-emon by then, I think?
当時の総一郎はもう偽右衛門であったかな
Yes, he was the leader who kept
.peace in Kyoto tanuki society.
はい
京都狸界をまとめ上げる頭領でありました
Atago                Shrine
The start of the the whole incident
そもそもの事件の発端は
was a fight between Nyoigatake Yakushibou here
.and the Kurama tengu.
こいつ 如意ヶ嶽薬師坊と鞍馬天狗の喧嘩だった
Those bumpkins were just trying to act cool.
山のどんぐりが格好を付けていやがる
ん？
ふん
んん
ああ　う あ
うああ
After making a total mess of the mountain,
both Yakushibou and the Kurama tengu
山を滅茶苦茶にしてしまった薬師坊と鞍馬天狗は
共に愛宕山太郎坊から大目玉を食らった
got a good scolding from
.Atagoyama Taroubou.
The Kurama whipped up
.their tengu winds first.
先に天狗風を吹かせたのは鞍馬の天狗どもだ
ふふふふふふ
You went and picked an unnecessary fight,
so it caused no end of trouble later on.
いらん喧嘩を売ったもんだから
後々大変だったろうに
Later on?
後々？
そのいざこざを根に持った鞍馬天狗たちがな
Those Kurama tengu who were
the root of the quarrel
took turns creeping onto Mount Nyoigatake
入れ替わり立ち替わり如意ヶ嶽へ潜り込んでは
and throwing "Give Yakushibou Hell" parties
.day in and day out, tormenting him.
薬師坊を徹底してバカにする会なるものを
連日連夜開催し
薬師坊を悩ませたのだ
くぬううううううう
はあ
ちじゃあ あ があ
はははは
その薬師坊の苦しみを見かねて立ち上がったのが
And who was it who, unable to bear Yakushibou's
suffering, decided to stand up for him?
ぐるるる
The tanuki known as
.Shimogamo Souichirou.
下鴨総一郎という狸であった
わあ
ああ ああ
うう う
あ あああ
ひい　うう ああ う う
うあ
う う
ううああ ああ ん ひ ひ
ひ ひ ひうう ああ
ひい ひい ひいい
パオーン
ええ
おお
パオーン
ひい ひい ひい ひい
とうとう野人と見分けが付かない
風体と成り果てた鞍馬天狗たちは
Finally, reduced to a state of pure,
instinctive fear, the Kurama tengu
prostrated themselves before
.Yakushibou and apologized.
薬師坊に土下座して謝った
In a feat of extraordinary magnificence,
何とも気宇壮大なことに
the tanuki Souichirou transformed into
.Mount Nyoigatake itself for an entire week.
総一郎という狸は一週間もの長きに渡り
如意ヶ嶽という山そのものに化けていたのだ
That's where the name
."False Nyoigatake Incident" comes from.
-これが偽如意ヶ嶽事件の名の由来だ
-ああ
Father sure was amazing, wasn't he?
お父さんって本当にすごかったんだね
Teakettle energy
Amazingly foolish, yes.
大した阿呆ではあったがな
ああ
あ
ん
You tanuki sure have it easy, lazily
.sleeping your days away like that.
のうのうと寝て暮らして狸というのは気楽なものだな
ん んん
I've gone and done something a little bit foolish.
いささか阿呆なことをしでかしまして
It was awfully entertaining but a bit
.too much excitement for one like me.
大変楽しゅうございましたが
あんまりはしゃぎ過ぎました
You shouldn't push yourself too hard.
ほどほどにすることだ
Take care.
養生せい
Thank you.
恐れ入ります
Teakettle energy
ずず
んん
あ
ああ　はははは
あはははは　ははは
あ
ああ
うっふふ
Benten is on the boat over there...
向こうの船に弁天様が
んん ぎぎ
Why?! Why does she spurn
the inner parlor I gave her
何故だ
何故わしが与えた奥座敷ではなく
毛玉の船なんぞに乗っておるのだ
only to ride on a boat with
those damned hairballs?!
Why won't she stay by my side?
何故わしの隣におらんのだ
Don't ask me.
知りませんよ
う
げほ ごほ
They always go overboard.
いくら何でもひど過ぎる
I'm going to give Uncle a piece of my mind.
俺が叔父上に抗議してこよう
わ ああ い
ああ
ん
わう
Cease this racket!
うるさいわ
はははは はーはーはー
く
Mother, please have some patience.
母上 ここは堪忍を
ええい いつもいつもこけにして
Dammit, they're always making fools of us!
We absolutely cannot retaliate!
こちらから手を出すのだけはいけません
There will be all kinds of troub—
いろいろと面倒が ごば う
んん
Let's hit them right between the eyes!
あの真ん中辺りがよろしいわ きっちり当てておやり
Take careful aim!
あ？
ん？
う う ほほ
ほっほー
ああ
ああ あん？
Why are you all just standing around?!
何ぼけっとしとる
あ
Yashiro!
矢四郎
Right!
ん
はああ 何ていうことを
How can you do that?!
True forbearance is tolerating the intolerable!
ならぬ堪忍するが堪忍
Drop dead!
くたばれ
あ いあ
ん んん
んん
んんふっ ん
It's about time we got out of here.
そろそろ逃げようぜ
ひい
Goodness! That would have killed me!
危ない 刺さったら死んじゃうでしょ
ひっひっひっひっひっひ
There we go. Now reel 'er in.
それ 引き寄せろ
Enemies in the same boat!
呉越同舟 呉越同舟
There are only a handful of 'em! Pull it in
real close, and fire everything we've got!
向こうは小勢だよ
しっかり引き付けて全部撃ち込んじゃえ
ええ ん
くう
は
うふ
ん？
ああ
Isn't there anything we can use?
何か無いのかい？
There's nothing here at all!
もう 何もありゃしない
は
Bring out Yaichirou, the heir!
総領の矢一郎を出してもらおう
That's not the heir at all!
.It's just the third son.
総領の代わりに三男坊が出てきたぞ
What happened to Yaichirou?
矢一郎はどうした？
Is he curled up in a ball
at the back of the room?
座敷の奥で縮こまっているのか
"You will have heard of me by now,
and here I am, before your very eyes:"
遠からん者は音にも聞け
近くには目にも見たまえ
The third son of Shimogamo
Souichirou, Yasaburou!
我こそは下鴨総一郎が三男
矢三郎なるぞ
We know that already!
んなことは分かっとるわ
Hurry up and bring out
.that big brother of yours.
早くあの兄貴を出せと言ってるんだ
We gotta thank him for chewing on
.our rear ends the other day, too.
この間お尻を噛まれたお礼もしなきゃならないしね
My butt nearly got an extra crack in it!
お尻が四つに割れるところだったよ
By the way, Yasaburou, how can you
persist in calling that a leisure cruiser?
それにしても矢三郎
これを納涼船と言い張るのは無理だね
That's not a boat, it's a tearoom!
これは船じゃなくて茶室じゃないかい
Being flamboyant is indeed the tanuki way,
いかに賑やかにやるのが狸の流儀とはいえ
but moderation is important as well.
節度が寛容でしょう
As a tanuki who upholds
the teachings of my father
面白かるべき行事を台無しにした
and lives purely and justly in this era of peace and tranquility,
不届き狸へお灸を据えてやるのは
父の教えを守って太平の世を
清く正しく生きる狸として
there is no doubt it is my duty
.to punish such out-of-line tanuki,
who ruined what should have
.been an enjoyable event.
当然の義務に違いありません
Are you okay?
大丈夫かお前？
構わん いてもうたれ
Who cares? Just go for it.
く
んん
あ
Well then, Uncle, I wish you well!
叔父上
ではご機嫌よう
ああ う う
あああああ
うう ああ ああうう
うあ　ああ
ああ
うう　あ うあ　くう
んん
Farewell, Ebisugawa!
さらば夷川
Isn't it grand to entrust yourself to the wind
and let yourself fall wherever it takes you?
風に任せていずちを指すともなく
落ちていくこそ嬉しけれ
べー
ん 狸というものは誠に救い難い阿呆だな
Tanuki truly are irredeemable fools.
All right, let's take a photo to commemorate.
よし 記念撮影をしよう
What a great family! I'm sure
.your father must be proud.
良い家族だ
父親も喜んでいるだろう
あ
あ 燃料が
The fuel is...
あ
Teakettle energy
げ んん？
く
ふ 無い
...gone!
ん 無いわよ
There's none here!
None here either!
無いよ
あああ 何ということだ
How could this be?!
At this rate, instead of being Nise-emon,
I'll end up a fallen tanuki!
このままでは偽右衛門どころか
潰れた狸になってしまう
うう
If we had just a little bit of port left...
ポートワインが少しでもあれば
ああ
あ？
Master, that's—
先生 それは
Why should I have to go
without my precious port
何故 茶釜ごときのために大事なポートワインを
我慢するいわれがあるのか
just for the sake of that blasted teakettle?!
I am your special guest this evening!
わしは今宵の大事なお客である
I'm greater than tanuki!
狸よりも偉いのである
Greater than that teakettle!
茶釜よりも偉いのである
I will drink as much as I want,
of whatever I want!
飲みたいものを好きに飲み
妄想の天空を自在に飛行するのは
What is soaring freely through the sky in one's
dreams, if not a tengu's natural right?!
天狗たるものの生得の権利に他ならぬ
I am Nyoigatake Yakushibou!
わしは
如意ヶ嶽薬師坊である　ん
ああ
はあ あ
ん ん ん　だあ
ああ
Ow...
あ ててて
Is everyone okay?
無事か
あ
I'm so sorry, but there was no way
.I could've carried all three of you.
いや すまんすまん
さすがに三人は無理じゃったわ
私は大丈夫ですけど
I'm all right, but... where's Master?
先生は？
んん
ず つつ
はあ
Though... this really isn't good.
しかし
これはまずい
ん
あ
はあ
ああ
It's not here! Or here! Or here!
無い
What isn't?
何がだ？
風神雷神の扇が
The Fuujin Raijin fan!
食べちゃいたいほど好きなのだもの
I like you so much I could just eat you up.
ふっふふふふ
If she actually liked me, that would be great.
それが本当ならば本望だ
But I really would not like to be eaten.
しかし
甚だ不本意
When all else fails, retreat!
三十六計逃げるにしかず
んん
Being the resourceful guy that
I am, I fled with such skill
才覚のある私は
あまりにも巧みに逃げたので
that from the end of summer into autumn,
夏の終わりから秋にかけて
I became renowned throughout Kyoto
as "Yasaburou the Fugitive."
私は
逃げの矢三郎という勇名を洛中に馳せることになる
繋いだ手を振りほどけば
You shake off my hand
tsunaida te wo furihodokeba
いたずらに　君微笑む
and idly smile at me
itazura ni kimi hohoemu
春は嵐　ざわざわする
Spring is ripe with the roll of thunder,
haru wa arashi zawazawa suru
もう花びら散りすぼんだ
and some cherry blossoms have already left the branches
mou hanabira chirisubonda
口癖はケセラセラ
Your favorite phrase is "Que será, será"
kuchiguse wa que sera sera
また呟く声がする
I can hear you whisper it again
mata tsubuyaku koe ga suru
彼女はいつもさよなら言わずに
She always vanishes
kanojo wa itsumo
sayonara
without saying "Goodbye,"
iwazu ni
風と消える
just like the wind
kaze to kieru
I don't know what the future will be like,
mirai no koto wa wakaranai keredo
未来のことはわからないけれど
今ここにある奇蹟は僕のものと
but I'll have faith
ima koko ni aru
that little miracles
kiseki wa
are awaiting me
boku no mono to shinjiteru
信じてる
約束なんてしたくないけれど
I don't want to be tied down by promises,
yakusoku nante shitakunai keredo
but let's hold up our hands
sono te wo kazashite
その手をかざして確かなもの
and find something,
tashika na mono
手に入れよう
something permanent
te ni ireyou
それは僕らを輝かす
that will
sore wa
show just who we are
bokura wo kagayakasu
I don't care whether you tell me
.the moon looks nice or not.
月が綺麗ですねと言われても
満月の夜は答えは同じ
On nights when the moon is full,
my response will always be the same.
だったら付き合って
So, come with me!
Next Time:
The Friday Fellows